{
  "level1": [
    {
      "question": "Malaria is transmitted ______",
      "option1": "Through mosquito bites",
      "option2": "By eating tainted food",
      "option3": "by physical contact",
      "option4": "By playing in dirt",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Malaria is prevented by ______",
      "option1": "Playing in dirt",
      "option2": "By not maintaining hygiene",
      "option3": "Sleeping under an insecticide-treated bednet",
      "option4": "By eating unprotected food",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following can repel mosquitoes?",
      "option1": "Banana",
      "option2": "Chilli",
      "option3": "Citronella",
      "option4": "Garlic",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these drink contains quinine, an anti-malarial property?",
      "option1": "Lemonade",
      "option2": "Tonic",
      "option3": "Warm milk",
      "option4": "Cola",
      "answer": "2"
    }
  ],
  "level2": [
    {
      "question": "Malaria is transmitted by a mosquito bite, but what causes the disease?",
      "option1": "Insecticide",
      "option2": "A virus",
      "option3": "Blood poisoning",
      "option4": "A parasite",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Find the odd symptom of malaria",
      "option1": "Fever",
      "option2": "Dizziness",
      "option3": "Fatigue",
      "option4": "Back pain",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Find the odd statement",
      "option1": "Malaria is a neglected tropical disease",
      "option2": "If you get malaria once, you won't ever get it again",
      "option3": "Malaria is quite often endemic in poorer regions of the world",
      "option4": "Malaria is not curable",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "Disease associated with malaria",
      "option1": "Jaundice",
      "option2": "Tuberculosis",
      "option3": "Cholera",
      "option4": "Typhoid",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "There are four kinds of malaria that can infect humans. They are all spread by what?",
      "option1": " a worm in the intestine",
      "option2": " a tick bite",
      "option3": " a mosquito bite",
      "option4": " a tsetse fly bite",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of the body do these malaria parasites feed on?",
      "option1": " intestinal lining",
      "option2": "muscles",
      "option3": "red blood cells",
      "option4": "brain tissue",
      "answer": "3"
    }
  ],
  "level3": [
    {
      "question": "How long must a malaria parasite grow in its host before infection can be spread to a human being?",
      "option1": " twenty four hours",
      "option2": "a week or more",
      "option3": "two weeks",
      "option4": "one month",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Once malaria parasites enter a person's blood they then travel to which organ?",
      "option1": "kidneys",
      "option2": "liver",
      "option3": "heart",
      "option4": "stomach",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Of the four types of malaria, 'falciparum malaria' is the most deadly. This type of malaria is most prevalent in what place?",
      "option1": "southeast Asia",
      "option2": "subSaharan Africa",
      "option3": "India",
      "option4": "South Africa",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many countries and territories worldwide are considered at risk for malarial infections?",
      "option1": "around 50",
      "option2": "more than 100",
      "option3": "fewer than 80",
      "option4": "exactly 65",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "According to the World Health Organization's estimate in 2000, malaria kills one child how often?",
      "option1": " every 15 minutes",
      "option2": " every minute",
      "option3": "every 30 seconds",
      "option4": "every five minutes",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "African children under the age of five suffer approximately how many bouts of malaria per year?",
      "option1": "10",
      "option2": "6",
      "option3": "12",
      "option4": "3",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of malaria is usually fatal?",
      "option1": " severe malaria",
      "option2": "cerebral malaria",
      "option3": "placental malaria",
      "option4": " all of the above",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "How soon, after infection, will a person feel usually begin to feel ill?",
      "option1": " 6 days",
      "option2": "2 days",
      "option3": "4 days",
      "option4": "none of the above",
      "answer": "4"
    }
  ]
}

